Yes, it's summer vacation now, right?
はい、今、夏休みでしたっけ?
This is my last year, after all.
最後の年ですよね、一応ね
May I ask your name, General?
一応名前聞いていいですか、大将?
May.
メイ
Mr. May.
メイさん
What I came here to do today is
今日、ここ何しに来たかっていうのは、
I understand.
分かってはいる
Do you feel like you know?
分かってはいるって感じですか?
Yeah.
うん
Is this your first time doing a shoot like this?
こういう撮影は初めてですか?
Are you a little nervous?
緊張多少してます?
yes.
はい
That's right.
ですよね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Now that it's summer vacation, are there any boyfriends at school?
今、夏休みだと、学校で彼氏とかはいないですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
not present?
いない?
Are you coming because you're not there?
いないから来てるのか
Have you ever had a boyfriend?
彼氏、いたことはある?
Yeah.
うん
How old were you when you experienced it for the first time?
それこそ、初体験とかって何歳ぐらいでした?
Well, relatively recently?
じゃあ結構、割と最近?
Do you remember?
覚えてます?
About that time.
その時のこととか
How would you describe it?
どんな感じって言いますか?
It's not good.
うまくじゃないですよ
Were you quite nervous?
結構、緊張したとか?
I haven't.
してない
してないですね
Or that it hurt.
とか、痛かったとか
It hurt.
痛かった
So, do you feel like it's relatively boring?
じゃあ、割とすんないって感じですか?
My boyfriend at the time?
彼氏、当時の?
That's right.
それはそう
そうなんですね
There are also people who aren't boyfriends.
彼氏じゃない人も、中にはいるんで
When it comes to sex, whether you like it or not,
セックスとか、好きか嫌いで言うと、
Do you like it?
好きですか?
Do you have any experience of doing something different?
今まで変わったところで、やった経験とかあります?
do not have.
ない
usually?
普通?
Usually at my boyfriend's house.
普通に彼氏の家とか
I don't really want to do that,
あ んまりそういうのしたいとかって、
I don't feel like it's anything special.
特にないって感じ
Normal is better.
普通がいい
You're young.
若いっすもんね
When I asked you whether you like sex or not,
さっきセックス、好きか嫌いかで言ったら、
You said you liked me, but if you really mean it...
好きって言ってましたけど、 大意とかで言うと、
Do you have a favorite meaning?
好きな大意とかってあります?
Feelings and feelings.
心情意とか
Normally?
普通に?
For example, if the other person is your boyfriend, you can see his face.
例えば、相手が彼氏とかだと、彼氏の顔が見えるからとか、
Or simply because it feels good when you hit a good spot.
あと単純に、いいとこ当たって気持ちいいからとか、
I think there are various reasons,
いろいろ理由はあると思うんですけど、
Is there a reason why you like Shinjoki?
心情意が好きな理由ってあります?
Because I'm wearing shoes.
靴を着るから
After all, if it's someone you like.
やっぱ、好きな人だったら
But my boyfriend, I see.
でも、彼氏、そうか
I said that I don't have that many partners and I don't have a boyfriend.
そんなに相手ない、彼氏いないって言ったけど、
Do you feel like you haven't had a boyfriend for that long?
そんなに、彼氏いない期間は、そんな長くないって感じですか?
Do you want it now, boyfriend?
今、欲しいんですか、彼氏?
Do you want it?
欲しいんですか?
Don't need it?
いらない?
why?
なんで?
Do you feel like that's the time now?
今はそういう時期って感じですか?
But is your boyfriend that kind of person?
でも、彼氏、そういう相手?
Who do you have sex with?
セックスする相手?
Of course, I think I only came here with my boyfriend.
もちろん、彼氏としかやってきてなかったと思うんですけど、
Don't you feel lonely when you're not there? It's those kind of nights.
いないと寂しくないですか、そういう夜というか
Do you want to feel horny?
ムラムラしたいとかないですか?
do not have.
ない
There isn't.
ないんだ
Well, that's it.
まあ、そんなもんか
Is there a big difference in age between boys and girls?
結 構、その年代って男子と女子で結構差ありますか?
May I ask you to stand there for once?
一回、そこに立ってみてもらっていいですか?
Aren't your legs extremely thin?
足とかめちゃくちゃ細くないですか?
Are you exercising?
運動してる?
Because I don't do much.
あんまりしてないから
Her stomach is amazing and flat.
お腹とかもすごい、ぺったんこじゃん
He's a nice guy, seriously.
いい感じの人だ、マジで
Squiggly?
すぐったい?
It's very sensitive.
めっちゃ敏感じゃん
Is it okay to wear over clothes?
服の上から大丈夫?
It's really good.
やっぱりすぐったい
Go ahead and become electronic.
結構、電子になれ
Are you the type who likes to be touched or tickled?
触られるとかすぐったいタイプ?
Seriously?
マジか
Just give me your hand.
ちょっと手を出して
If I continue like this, will my clothes get dirty?
このままだとあれで、服汚れちゃう?
Take it off?
脱ぐ?
Try spreading your legs a little.
ちょっと足広げてみて
It's very sensitive.
めっちゃ敏感じゃん
I think that's why I'm so sensitive.
それが敏感なんだなって思って
This sort of thing is also ticklish.
こういうのもくすぐったいからな
Do you usually use it?
普段使う?
I've been tickling here for a long time, I guess.
ここにずっとくすぐったよね、多分
Wow.
うわーって
Maybe around here?
ここ多分、この辺は?
It's so good.
すぐったい
Is it okay here?
ここ大丈夫?
It wasn't surprising.
不思議じゃなかった
一番敏感層
teeth?
は?
I can't tell, so I don't know where to start.
言 えないから、どこ当てればいいのか分かんない
Is it ticklish here too?
ここにもくすぐったいのか?
Isn't it ticklish here too?
ここにもくすぐったくない?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Did it hurt?
痛かった?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くはない?
There's something wrong with my body...
体がなんか...
I really reacted.
めっちゃ反応したよ
Please tell me a little bit about what happened.
何があったかちょっと教えてください
It wasn't that it hurt.
痛かったわけじゃない
So what happened?
じゃあ何があった?
If anything, did it feel good?
どっちかと言えば気持ちよかった?
I'm already exhausted though.
すでにぐったりしてるけど
I'm not feeling better though.
俺 は気持ちよくなってないんだけど
I'm exhausted though.
ぐったりしてるけど
Don't sleep like that.
そのまま寝ないでよ
Mi-chan, do you know what a crotch is?
みーちゃんさ、 股とかって分かる?
how...
どうやって...
Will you?
するの?
how?
どうやって?
Straddling...
またがって...
difficult.
難しい
Have you never done it?
やったことない?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
How do you rub it?
どうやって擦るの?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Move your hips...
腰を動かして...
difficult.
難しい
bean paste
あん
Mari, have you never done it?
まり やったことない?
Yeah.
うん
I'm really worried.
めっちゃ心配
Thighs?
太もも?
Have you never done this before?
これもやったことない?
Yeah.
うん
This is not enough...
これだけじゃ足りなくてさ...
It's free.
自由だよ
Well, I don't know.
えー、分からん
I can't get in.
入らん
it hurts?
痛い?
this.
これ
Cum inside me.
中出して